{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200384132","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200384132"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" f53f8b25-106e-4659-a779-f68a3ef21a32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-1-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200389695","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200389695"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" f53f8b25-106e-4659-a779-f68a3ef21a32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-1-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200395224","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200395224"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" f53f8b25-106e-4659-a779-f68a3ef21a32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-4-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200400431","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200400431"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" f53f8b25-106e-4659-a779-f68a3ef21a32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-4-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200406728","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200406728"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" f53f8b25-106e-4659-a779-f68a3ef21a32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_2-4-3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200411996","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200411996"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" f53f8b25-106e-4659-a779-f68a3ef21a32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_2-4-3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200435391","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200435391"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" f53f8b25-106e-4659-a779-f68a3ef21a32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_2-4-1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200442816","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200442816"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" f53f8b25-106e-4659-a779-f68a3ef21a32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_2-4-1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200448117","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200448117"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" f53f8b25-106e-4659-a779-f68a3ef21a32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_2-4-1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200459068","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200459067"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" f53f8b25-106e-4659-a779-f68a3ef21a32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-2"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200465265","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200465265"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" f53f8b25-106e-4659-a779-f68a3ef21a32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-4-2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200470550","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200470550"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" f53f8b25-106e-4659-a779-f68a3ef21a32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-4-2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200481696","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200481695"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" f53f8b25-106e-4659-a779-f68a3ef21a32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-4-1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200488845","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200488845"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" f53f8b25-106e-4659-a779-f68a3ef21a32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-1-4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200495190","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200495190"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" f53f8b25-106e-4659-a779-f68a3ef21a32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-1-4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200501362","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200501362"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" f53f8b25-106e-4659-a779-f68a3ef21a32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200517119","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200517118"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" f53f8b25-106e-4659-a779-f68a3ef21a32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200527057","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200527057"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" f53f8b25-106e-4659-a779-f68a3ef21a32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200535511","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200535511"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" f53f8b25-106e-4659-a779-f68a3ef21a32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-1-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200542105","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200542105"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" f53f8b25-106e-4659-a779-f68a3ef21a32"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-1-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200576514","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200576514"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" a71cccfc-55ab-46e4-88f6-5a1dd033167f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-1-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200582456","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200582456"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" a71cccfc-55ab-46e4-88f6-5a1dd033167f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-2-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200597448","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200597448"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" a71cccfc-55ab-46e4-88f6-5a1dd033167f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-3-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200602847","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200602847"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" a71cccfc-55ab-46e4-88f6-5a1dd033167f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-3-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200607683","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200607682"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" a71cccfc-55ab-46e4-88f6-5a1dd033167f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-3-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200615883","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200615883"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" a71cccfc-55ab-46e4-88f6-5a1dd033167f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-1-3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200618157","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200618156"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" a71cccfc-55ab-46e4-88f6-5a1dd033167f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-1-3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200633315","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200633315"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 12b3f9d2-8f00-4594-a628-30e4afe3fd4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-3-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200638510","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200638510"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 12b3f9d2-8f00-4594-a628-30e4afe3fd4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-1-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200646831","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200646831"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 12b3f9d2-8f00-4594-a628-30e4afe3fd4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-1-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200654722","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200654722"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 12b3f9d2-8f00-4594-a628-30e4afe3fd4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-1-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200661593","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200661593"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 12b3f9d2-8f00-4594-a628-30e4afe3fd4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_2-4-1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200666532","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200666532"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 12b3f9d2-8f00-4594-a628-30e4afe3fd4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_2-4-1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200674448","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200674448"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 12b3f9d2-8f00-4594-a628-30e4afe3fd4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-3-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200681735","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200681735"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 12b3f9d2-8f00-4594-a628-30e4afe3fd4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-3-4"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200688177","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200688177"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 12b3f9d2-8f00-4594-a628-30e4afe3fd4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-4-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200694636","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200694636"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 12b3f9d2-8f00-4594-a628-30e4afe3fd4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_2-4-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200702868","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200702868"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 12b3f9d2-8f00-4594-a628-30e4afe3fd4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-3-2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200708983","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200708983"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 12b3f9d2-8f00-4594-a628-30e4afe3fd4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-3-2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200713904","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200713904"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 12b3f9d2-8f00-4594-a628-30e4afe3fd4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-3-2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200720506","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200720506"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 12b3f9d2-8f00-4594-a628-30e4afe3fd4c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-3-2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200748980","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200748980"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 48921903-824c-4b51-91db-1297f304c4e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-1-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200750347","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200750347"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 48921903-824c-4b51-91db-1297f304c4e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-1-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200768858","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200768857"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 442c49f7-171a-4fa8-8c27-77a804e50a03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-O-U"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200773555","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200773554"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 442c49f7-171a-4fa8-8c27-77a804e50a03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-O-U"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200875786","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200875786"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 442c49f7-171a-4fa8-8c27-77a804e50a03"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-O-U"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200875878","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200875878"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" b5eb4337-6b4a-4178-af7a-8c5abce00e1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200884938","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200884937"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" b5eb4337-6b4a-4178-af7a-8c5abce00e1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200893833","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200893833"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" b5eb4337-6b4a-4178-af7a-8c5abce00e1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..A.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200911779","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200911779"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" b5eb4337-6b4a-4178-af7a-8c5abce00e1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200920753","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200920752"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" b5eb4337-6b4a-4178-af7a-8c5abce00e1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200929852","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200929852"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" b5eb4337-6b4a-4178-af7a-8c5abce00e1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200941894","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200941894"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" b5eb4337-6b4a-4178-af7a-8c5abce00e1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::vow.A..Z.asc.uc.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549200949468","data":{"timestamp":" 1549200949468"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" b5eb4337-6b4a-4178-af7a-8c5abce00e1a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_4"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Huwaalika watoto kuangalia runinga katika duka lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201016897","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201016897"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 8751465a-da7a-4f2a-beea-3ba537946ae1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201110774","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201110773"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 8751465a-da7a-4f2a-beea-3ba537946ae1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201110894","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201110893"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 8751465a-da7a-4f2a-beea-3ba537946ae1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201124909","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201124908"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 05b1713b-812d-4751-8e2c-8a7a6727077d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ENDESHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDESHA"," userResponse":" ENDESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201131040","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201131039"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 05b1713b-812d-4751-8e2c-8a7a6727077d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ENDESHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDESHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201132613","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201132613"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 05b1713b-812d-4751-8e2c-8a7a6727077d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ELIMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" ELIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201135549","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201135549"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 05b1713b-812d-4751-8e2c-8a7a6727077d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ELIMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" ELIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201137141","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201137141"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 05b1713b-812d-4751-8e2c-8a7a6727077d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201144932","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201144932"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 05b1713b-812d-4751-8e2c-8a7a6727077d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201146976","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201146976"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 05b1713b-812d-4751-8e2c-8a7a6727077d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201147145","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201147145"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 05b1713b-812d-4751-8e2c-8a7a6727077d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201160382","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201160381"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 6e2d553f-e6fc-4b26-a4fe-3ba778cd54e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201165957","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201165956"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 6e2d553f-e6fc-4b26-a4fe-3ba778cd54e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201167881","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201167881"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 6e2d553f-e6fc-4b26-a4fe-3ba778cd54e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201180773","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201180773"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 6e2d553f-e6fc-4b26-a4fe-3ba778cd54e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201191924","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201191924"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 6e2d553f-e6fc-4b26-a4fe-3ba778cd54e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201203508","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201203507"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 6e2d553f-e6fc-4b26-a4fe-3ba778cd54e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201216372","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201216372"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" e818595a-de9a-402e-ae96-817e183dc4b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201216850","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201216850"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" e818595a-de9a-402e-ae96-817e183dc4b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201216994","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201216994"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" e818595a-de9a-402e-ae96-817e183dc4b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201227113","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201227113"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" e818595a-de9a-402e-ae96-817e183dc4b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201243703","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201243702"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" e818595a-de9a-402e-ae96-817e183dc4b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201251761","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201251761"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" e818595a-de9a-402e-ae96-817e183dc4b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201273403","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201273403"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 74631f3a-1d0d-4935-b9d3-28be223735a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201275142","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201275142"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 74631f3a-1d0d-4935-b9d3-28be223735a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201279107","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201279107"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 74631f3a-1d0d-4935-b9d3-28be223735a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201280890","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201280890"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 74631f3a-1d0d-4935-b9d3-28be223735a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201282953","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201282953"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 74631f3a-1d0d-4935-b9d3-28be223735a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201291844","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201291843"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 74631f3a-1d0d-4935-b9d3-28be223735a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201291845","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201291844"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 74631f3a-1d0d-4935-b9d3-28be223735a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201292145","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201292144"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 74631f3a-1d0d-4935-b9d3-28be223735a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201303175","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201303175"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 74631f3a-1d0d-4935-b9d3-28be223735a5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.reveal__1..4.SS_OFF1_DES.29"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201382496","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201382496"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa_kuu-mdomo-anga-chungwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chungwa"," userResponse":" chungwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201399477","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201399477"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa_bata-chungwa-naam-zama"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chungwa"," userResponse":" chungwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201435238","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201435238"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" manjano_manjano-kali-samahani-hizi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" manjano"," userResponse":" manjano"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201465159","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201465159"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" manjano_a-manjano-u-maridadi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" manjano"," userResponse":" manjano"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201506701","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201506701"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kijani_kijani-gani-taratibu-hebu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kijani"," userResponse":" kijani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201524837","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201524837"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kijani_je-kijani-kasi-macho"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kijani"," userResponse":" kijani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201546749","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201546748"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samawati_ngoja-fulani-samawati-maridadi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" samawati"," userResponse":" maridadi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201550756","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201550756"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samawati_ngoja-fulani-samawati-maridadi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" samawati"," userResponse":" fulani"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201561975","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201561975"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samawati_ngoja-fulani-samawati-maridadi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" samawati"," userResponse":" ngoja"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201564755","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201564755"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samawati_ngoja-fulani-samawati-maridadi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" samawati"," userResponse":" samawati"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201582637","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201582637"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samawati_ndipo-damu-kavu-samawati"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" samawati"," userResponse":" kavu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201586470","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201586470"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samawati_ndipo-damu-kavu-samawati"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" samawati"," userResponse":" damu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201597322","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201597322"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samawati_ndipo-damu-kavu-samawati"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" samawati"," userResponse":" ndipo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201601156","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201601156"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samawati_ndipo-damu-kavu-samawati"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" samawati"," userResponse":" samawati"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201626443","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201626443"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nili_vingine-yu-bwawa-nili"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nili"," userResponse":" yu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201630557","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201630557"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nili_vingine-yu-bwawa-nili"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nili"," userResponse":" vingine"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201636052","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201636052"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nili_vingine-yu-bwawa-nili"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nili"," userResponse":" bwawa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201639464","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201639464"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nili_vingine-yu-bwawa-nili"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nili"," userResponse":" nili"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201661000","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201661000"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nili_pumua-kaka-nili-kadhaa"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nili"," userResponse":" nili"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201680226","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201680226"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zambarau_zambarau-cheza-taja-ata"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" zambarau"," userResponse":" ata"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201684990","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201684989"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zambarau_zambarau-cheza-taja-ata"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" zambarau"," userResponse":" taja"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201688603","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201688603"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zambarau_zambarau-cheza-taja-ata"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" zambarau"," userResponse":" zambarau"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201709391","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201709390"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zambarau_zambarau-cheza-taja-ata"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201709598","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201709598"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" d37c94c1-c900-422a-8684-d9cc9a80fa19"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za ____________?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201731264","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201731263"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" c0e48457-bffb-4a78-9fcc-d4f6c955691d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_I_O"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201738850","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201738850"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" c0e48457-bffb-4a78-9fcc-d4f6c955691d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_I_O"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:vow.ltr.uc:E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201741638","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201741637"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" c0e48457-bffb-4a78-9fcc-d4f6c955691d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_vow.ltr.uc_E..E.vow.10.rand.say.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_E_I_O"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_INC.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201758444","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201758443"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" ec1064be-0b45-4ee6-8933-ff57f330e8e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_INC.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFURI"," userResponse":" SIFURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_INC.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201761618","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201761617"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" ec1064be-0b45-4ee6-8933-ff57f330e8e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_INC.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFURI"," userResponse":" SIFURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_INC.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201763928","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201763928"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" ec1064be-0b45-4ee6-8933-ff57f330e8e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_INC.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_INC.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201764753","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201764753"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" ec1064be-0b45-4ee6-8933-ff57f330e8e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_INC.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201765000","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201765000"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" ec1064be-0b45-4ee6-8933-ff57f330e8e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_INC.3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201776805","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201776805"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 11d81bed-8247-4570-8a0f-ce5973ed7e85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201777195","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201777195"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 11d81bed-8247-4570-8a0f-ce5973ed7e85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201777432","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201777432"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 11d81bed-8247-4570-8a0f-ce5973ed7e85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201777756","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201777756"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 11d81bed-8247-4570-8a0f-ce5973ed7e85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201777995","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201777995"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 11d81bed-8247-4570-8a0f-ce5973ed7e85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A E I O U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201781485","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201781485"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 11d81bed-8247-4570-8a0f-ce5973ed7e85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201781792","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201781792"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 11d81bed-8247-4570-8a0f-ce5973ed7e85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201782695","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201782695"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 11d81bed-8247-4570-8a0f-ce5973ed7e85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201783119","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201783119"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 11d81bed-8247-4570-8a0f-ce5973ed7e85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549201783521","data":{"timestamp":" 1549201783521"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20190203_162609"," gameId":" 11d81bed-8247-4570-8a0f-ce5973ed7e85"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__UC_Vowel_Song_1__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}